Guide to the Walter Chauncey Camp Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1875 - 1925; Series I; 13 linear feet (31 boxes)
  - Loury, Francis, [1894] (Box 16, Folder 437)
  - Loveland, John C., 1894 (Box 16, Folder 437)
  - Lovewell, Charles H., Jr., 1894 (Box 16, Folder 437)
  - Low, William E., Jr., 1905 (Box 16, Folder 438)
  - Lowell, James A.(*), 1889, undated (Box 16, Folder 438)
  - Lowndes, Mrs. R. T., Jr., undated (Box 16, Folder 438)
  - Low's (Edwin H.) Steamship Agency, 1907 (Box 16, Folder 438)
  - Lum, William Tappan, 1911 (Box 16, Folder 439)
  - Lunsford, H. A., 1900 (Box 16, Folder 439)
  - Lunt, W. D., 1921 (Box 16, Folder 439)
  - Luther, F. S., 1894-1896 (Box 16, Folder 439)
  - Luther, Willard B., 1905-1906 (Box 16, Folder 439)
  - Lydon, Joseph William, 1905 (Box 16, Folder 439)
  - Lyman, Chester W., 1894 (Box 16, Folder 439)
  - Lyons, Eddie, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 439)
  - Lyons, Leo V., 1916 (Box 16, Folder 439)
  - McAdoo, William G.(*), 1917-1919 (Box 16, Folder 440)
  - McAllister, Hall, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 441)
  - McAlpin, Henry, 1894 (Box 16, Folder 441)
  - McAndrew, Alexander, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 441)
  - McArthur, Clifton N.(*), 1902-1910 (Box 16, Folder 442)
  - McArthur, Clifton N.(*), 1915-1920 (Box 16, Folder 443)
  - McAsham, H. N., 1911 (Box 16, Folder 444)
  - Macaudirn, David Carr, 1898 (Box 16, Folder 444)
  - McAvoy, George L., 1896, undated (Box 16, Folder 444)
  - McBride, C. E., 1909 (Box 16, Folder 445)
  - McBride, Herbert, 1894 (Box 16, Folder 445)
  - McBride, Malcolm Lee(*), 1894-1900, 1909-1920 (Box 16, Folder 445)
  - McCabe, W. G., 1894 (Box 16, Folder 446)
  - McClenahan, Howard, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 446)
  - McClung, Thomas Lee(*), 1891-1894, 1910-1911, undated (Box 16, Folder 447)
  - McClure, Charles R., 1909 (Box 16, Folder 448)
  - McClure, James G. K., 1894 (Box 16, Folder 448)
  - McClure, S. S., 1891-1897 (Box 16, Folder 448)
  - McCook, Anson T., 1910-1911, 1913, undated (Box 16, Folder 449)
  - McCormick, Medill, 1908 (Box 16, Folder 450)
  - McCormick, Robert R., 1914 (Box 16, Folder 450)
  - McCormick, Vance C.(*), 1892-1922 (Box 16, Folder 451-453)
  - McCornack, Walter E., 1902 (Box 16, Folder 454)
  - McCosh, A. J., 1894 (Box 16, Folder 454)
  - McCracken, J. C., 1899 (Box 16, Folder 454)
  - McCurdy, J. H., 1905 (Box 16, Folder 454)
  - McCutchen, S. St. J., 1893 (Box 16, Folder 454)
  - McDavitt, Clarance G., 1900, 1908, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 455)
  - McDonald, J., 1924 (Box 16, Folder 455)
  - McDonald, J. C., 1916 (Box 16, Folder 455)
  - McDonell, J. Osborne, 1910 (Box 16, Folder 456)
  - McDonnell, R. A., 1899, 1907 (Box 16, Folder 456)
  - McFadden, George H., 1906 (Box 17, Folder 457)
  - McFadden Publications, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 457)
  - McGaffey, Ernest, 1900 (Box 17, Folder 458)
  - McGugin, Dan E.(*), 1906-1923 (Box 17, Folder 458)
  - McKee, Oliver, 1896, 1900 (Box 17, Folder 459)
  - Mackenzie, Charles S., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 459)
  - Mackenzie, James C., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 459)
  - Mackenzie, John P., 1893 (Box 17, Folder 459)
  - McKenzie, R. Tait, 1911 (Box 17, Folder 459)
  - Mackey, H. A., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 459)
  - McKinley, Stone & Mackenzie, undated (Box 17, Folder 460)
  - McKinney, W. W., 1916 (Box 17, Folder 460)
  - McLain - Simpers Organization, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 460)
  - McLanahan, George X., 1908 (Box 17, Folder 460)
  - McLane, W. L., 1895 (Box 17, Folder 460)
  - McLaren, James W., 1898 (Box 17, Folder 460)
  - McLemore, M. C., Jr., 1893 (Box 17, Folder 461)
  - Macmillan Company, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 461)
  - McMillan, P. H., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 461)
  - MacNair, Theodore M., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 461)
  - McNitt, V. V., 1915, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 461)
  - McRae, Archibald N., 1908 (Box 17, Folder 462)
  - Macrae, John D., 1893 (Box 17, Folder 462)
  - Macreadie, A. S., 1907 (Box 17, Folder 462)
  - McWilliams & Arthur Co., 1900 (Box 17, Folder 462)
  - Madeira, Louis C., Jr., 1898 (Box 17, Folder 463)
  - Maffitt, William, 1900, undated (Box 17, Folder 463)
  - Magidsohn, Joseph, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 463)
  - Mairs, George H., 1921 (Box 17, Folder 464)
  - Manassas Industrial School, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 464)
  - Manhattan Athletic Club, 1891 (Box 17, Folder 464)
  - Manhattan Press Clipping Bureau, 1891 (Box 17, Folder 464)
  - Manley, Edward, 1900, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 464)
  - Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 464)
  - March, Francis A., Jr., 1900 (Box 17, Folder 465)
  - March, Moncure, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 465)
  - Marietta College Athletic Association, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 465)
  - Marquis (A. N.) & Company, 1898 (Box 17, Folder 465)
  - Marshall, Henry, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 465)
  - Martaw, Kenneth, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 465)
  - Martin, Louis, 1893 (Box 17, Folder 466)
  - Martin, William T., 1916 (Box 17, Folder 466)
  - Marting, H. A., 1917 (Box 17, Folder 466)
  - Marting, William, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 466)
  - Marvin, Reginald K., 1913-1915 (Box 17, Folder 466)
  - Mason, Edward G., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 467)
  - Mason, George G.(*), 1911-1912, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 467)
  - Mason, H. D., Jr., 1905-1909 (Box 17, Folder 468)
  - Mason, Roy
    See: box 9, folder 251-253
  - Matches, W., 1917 (Box 17, Folder 469)
  - Mathewson, Charles F.(*), 1890, 1895, 1903-1913 (Box 17, Folder 469)
  - Mattoon, Albert W.(*), 1917-1918 (Box 17, Folder 470)
  - Maxwell, Robert W., 1919 (Box 17, Folder 471)
  - Mayer, Harry C., 1893 (Box 17, Folder 471)
  - Maynard Press Agency, 1900-1902 (Box 17, Folder 471)
  - Mayser, Charles W., 1908, 1911 (Box 17, Folder 471)
  - Meade, P. R., 1898 (Box 17, Folder 472)
  - Mechling, Edward A., 1899 (Box 17, Folder 472)
  - Medical Times, 1914, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 472)
  - Meehan, John F., 1922 (Box 17, Folder 472)
  - Meiklejohn, Alexander, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 472)
  - Mellett, John Calvin, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 472)
  - Melton, B. B., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 472)
  - Mendell, Clarence W., 1919, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 472)
  - Mercer, E.C., 1910 (Box 17, Folder 473)
  - Mercer University, 1892 (Box 17, Folder 473)
  - Mercersburg Academy, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 473)
  - Merchants Club (Boston), 1895 (Box 17, Folder 473)
  - Meriden (Connecticut) City of, 1893, 1904-1905 (Box 17, Folder 473)
  - Meriden Daily Journal, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 473)
  - Merrell, C. A., 1903, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 474)
  - Merriam, G. A., 1891-1893, 1896 (Box 17, Folder 474)
  - Merriam, James F., 1909 (Box 17, Folder 474)
  - Merrill, Elmer Truesdell, 1894-1895 (Box 17, Folder 474)
  - Merrill, Moses, 1894 (Box 17, Folder 474)
  - Merrill, Paul, 1894 (Box 17, Folder 474)
  - Merriman, D. W., 1916 (Box 17, Folder 474)
  - Merriman, Edward D., 1908 (Box 17, Folder 474)
  - Merwin, Samuel, 1898 (Box 17, Folder 474)
  - Messler, Eugene, 1894 (Box 17, Folder 475)
  - Metcalf, Edwin D., 1902 (Box 17, Folder 475)
  - Metropolitan Newspaper Service, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 475)
  - Metzger, Sol, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 475)
  - Meyer, Christopher, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 475)
  - Michell, J. H., [1894] (Box 17, Folder 476)
  - Michigan Alumnus, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 476)
  - Michigan, University of, 1912, 1923, undated (Box 17, Folder 476)
  - Middleton, Caleb S., 1902 (Box 17, Folder 476)
  - Middleton, W. H., 1909 (Box 17, Folder 476)
  - Miel, E., 1887 (Box 17, Folder 476)
  - Miles, George W., Jr., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 477)
  - Miles, Harry R., undated (Box 17, Folder 477)
  - Milestones, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 477)
  - Military Order of the World War, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 477)
  - Miller, Edward M., 1924 (Box 17, Folder 477)
  - Miller, F. S., 1889 (Box 17, Folder 477)
  - Miller, Roy J., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 477)
  - Miller, Sidney, 1906 (Box 17, Folder 477)
  - Milliken, C. S., 1905 (Box 17, Folder 478)
  - Mills, Charles B., 1917, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 478)
  - Mills, Matthew, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 478)
  - Milton Academy, 1894 (Box 17, Folder 478)
  - Miner, E. D., 1906 (Box 17, Folder 479)
  - Minneapolis Athletic Conference, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 479)
  - Minneapolis Journal, 1899, [1905?] (Box 17, Folder 479)
  - Minnesota, University of, 1892, 1915 (Box 17, Folder 479)
  - Minor, Harry, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 479)
  - Mississippi A & M College, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 480)
  - Mississippi Merchants Association, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 480)
  - Missouri, University of, 1900-1901, 1910, undated (Box 17, Folder 480)
  - Mitchell, Edwin Knox, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 480)
  - Mitchell, L., 1920 (Box 17, Folder 480)
  - Moffat, Alexander(*), 1893-1899, 1902-1905, undated (Box 17, Folder 481)
  - Moffat, W. D., 1916, undated (Box 17, Folder 481)
    See also: box 17, folder 482
  - Moffat Yard & Company, 1911-1916-1917, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 482)
  - Moise, H. D., Jr., 1900 (Box 17, Folder 483)
  - Monahan, O. F., 1910 (Box 17, Folder 483)
  - Monilaw, William J., 1907-1908 (Box 17, Folder 483)
  - Monosmith, L. C., 1916 (Box 17, Folder 483)
  - Montclair Academy Athletic Association, 1910 (Box 17, Folder 483)
  - Moody, Farley W., 1915 (Box 17, Folder 484)
  - Moody, W. R., 1910, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 484)
  - Moon, (Byron G.) Co.(*), 1923 (Box 17, Folder 485)
  - Moore, Fred W., 1916, 1922-1923 (Box 17, Folder 486)
  - Moore, J. Malcolm, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 486)
  - Moore, John E., 1900 (Box 17, Folder 486)
  - Moorhead, John, Jr., 1894, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 486)
  - Moran, Thomas F., 1910-1911 (Box 17, Folder 487)
  - Morgan, D. Percy, 1894-1995 (Box 17, Folder 487)
  - Morgan, J. E., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 487)
  - Morgan, Ralph, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 487)
  - Morgan, W. C., Jr., 1889 (Box 17, Folder 487)
  - Morice, William N.(*), 1905-1906, 1910, 1913-1917, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 488)
  - Morison, George B., 1894 (Box 18, Folder 489)
  - Morison, R. N., 1894 (Box 18, Folder 489)
  - Mork, C. O., 1899 (Box 18, Folder 489)
  - Morley, William R., 1903 (Box 18, Folder 489)
  - Morrey, Charles B., 1892 (Box 18, Folder 490)
  - Morris, Charles G., 1900 (Box 18, Folder 490)
  - Morris, E. P., 1906 (Box 18, Folder 490)
  - Morris, Frank G., 1916 (Box 18, Folder 490)
  - Morris, Governeur, 1902 (Box 18, Folder 490)
  - Morris, John S., 1921 (Box 18, Folder 490)
  - Morrison, F. S., 1905 (Box 18, Folder 490)
  - Morrow, Thomas R., 1913 (Box 18, Folder 490)
  - Morse, Richard C., 1889, 1893 (Box 18, Folder 491)
  - Morse, Sam, 1906, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 491)
  - Morse, Samuel F. B., 1912 (Box 18, Folder 491)
  - Morse, W. H., 1919 (Box 18, Folder 491)
  - Mortimer, Mrs. R. G., 1904 (Box 18, Folder 492)
  - Morton, Charles H., 1900 (Box 18, Folder 492)
  - Morton, Marcus, [1907] (Box 18, Folder 492)
  - Mosle, A. Henry, 1892, undated (Box 18, Folder 492)
  - Moss, Earle W., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 492)
  - Moss, Edward B., 1917 (Box 18, Folder 492)
  - Moss, S. R., 1903 (Box 18, Folder 492)
  - Mosse, Arthur, 1908-1909 (Box 18, Folder 493)
  - Motor Life, 1919 (Box 18, Folder 494)
  - Mount, F. W., 1893 (Box 18, Folder 494)
  - Mount Union College, 1914 (Box 18, Folder 494)
  - Mudie, Howard, 1900 (Box 18, Folder 495)
  - Munro, W. H., 1899 (Box 18, Folder 495)
  - Munroe, Kirk, 1902 (Box 18, Folder 495)
  - Munsell, Joel, undated (Box 18, Folder 495)
  - Murphy, B. R., 1919 (Box 18, Folder 496)
  - Murphy, Fred J., 1914 (Box 18, Folder 496)
  - Murphy, Fred T.(*), 1896, 1899-1920 (Box 18, Folder 497)
  - Murphy, Fred W., 1916 (Box 18, Folder 498)
  - Murphy, Grayson M. P., 1919 (Box 18, Folder 498)
  - Murphy, Mallie J., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 498)
  - Murphy, Mike, 1906,1910 (Box 18, Folder 498)
  - Murphy, Thomas F., 1908, undated (Box 18, Folder 498)
  - Murphy, W. H., 1892 (Box 18, Folder 498)
  - Myrick, Julian S., 1918, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 499)
  - Nast, Conde, 1898, 1900 (Box 18, Folder 500)
    See also: box 6, folder 162-181 See also: box 25, folder 719
  - National Civic Federation, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 500)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association(*), 1911-1925 (Box 18, Folder 500)
  - National Committee of Patriotic Societies, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 501)
  - National Friends of Boys, 1909 (Box 18, Folder 501)
  - Natinal Information Bureau, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 501)
  - National Inter-Scholastic Association, 1906 (Box 18, Folder 501)
  - National Junior Sport League, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 501)
  - National League Baseball Clubs, 1883, undated (Box 18, Folder 502)
  - National Out-Door Sports Exposition, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 502)
  - National Physical Education Service(*), 1919-1923, undated (Box 18, Folder 503)
  - National Press Agency, 1900 (Box 18, Folder 504)
  - National Security League(*), 1917-1920 (Box 18, Folder 504)
  - National Service, 1917 (Box 18, Folder 504)
  - Navy League of the United States, 1917 (Box 18, Folder 504)
  - Neal, Mrs. C. J., 1905 (Box 18, Folder 505)
  - Nebraska, University of, 1892, 1899 (Box 18, Folder 505)
  - Nelson (Thomas) & Sons, 1910-1911 (Box 18, Folder 505)
  - Nesser, Theodore, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 505)
  - Nettleton, Walter, undated (Box 18, Folder 505)
  - Neumann, Paul, 1899 (Box 18, Folder 505)
  - Nevins, H. B., 1895 (Box 18, Folder 505)
  - New Britain College Club, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 506)
  - New Britain (Connecticut) High School
    See: box 20, folder 566
  - New Hampshire College, 1908 (Box 19, Folder 506)
  - New Haven Manufacturers' Exhibit, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 506)
  - New Haven Register, 1894, 1917, undated (Box 19, Folder 506)
  - New Haven Society Blue Book, 1915 (Box 19, Folder 506)
  - New Rochelle Parent-Teacher Association, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 506)
  - New York American, 1905-1923 (Box 19, Folder 507)
  - New York Central & Hudson River Railroad Co., 1901 (Box 19, Folder 507)
  - New York Evening Post, undated (Box 19, Folder 507)
  - New York Evening Telegram, 1896 (Box 19, Folder 507)
  - New York Herald (*), 1891-1922, undated (Box 19, Folder 508)
  - New York Sun, 1903, 1917, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 508)
  - New York Times, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 508)
  - New York Tribune, 1908, 1910-1911 (Box 19, Folder 508)
  - New York University, 1896 (Box 19, Folder 509)
  - New York, University of the State of, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 509)
  - New York World, [1894], 1905-1917 (Box 19, Folder 509)
  - Newcombe, C. H., 1893 (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Newell, A. B., 1894 (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Newhall, D. S., 1891 (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Newspaper Enterprise Association, 1911, 1919 (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Newton, Byron R., 1917-1919 (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Newton, Jesse, 1902 (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Newton, S. B., 1899, 1906-1911, undated (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Nichols, Charles P., 1890 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Nichols, G. E., 1920 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Nichols, George, 1900 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Nichols, Thomas F., 1902 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Nicholson, Thomas B., 1920 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Nicolson, Frank W., 1905 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Nielsen, Fred K., 1907, 1909-1910 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Nixon, William W. K., 1894 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Noble, Edward I., 1905 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - Nolan, William J., 1910 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - Norcross, F. S., Jr., 1908 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - North American, 1902 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - North Carolina College of Agriculture & Mechanic Arts, 1900 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - North Carolina, University of, 1893, 1903 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - North Dakota, State University of, 1900 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - Northern Newspaper Syndicate, 1900 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - Northward-Ho!, 1910, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - Notre Dame, University of, 1892 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - Novagraph Film Corporation, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 513)
  - Noyes, Edward W., 1902 (Box 19, Folder 513)
  - Noyes, Robert H., 1907 (Box 19, Folder 513)
  - Nurse, J. H., 1902 (Box 19, Folder 513)
  - Oakland Tribune, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 514)
  - Ober, Birch R., undated (Box 19, Folder 514)
  - Oberlin College(*), 1909-1923, undated (Box 19, Folder 514)
  - Ocean Accident & Guarantee Corp., LTD, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 514)
  - Official Golf Guide, undated (Box 19, Folder 514)
  - Ogden (Utah) High School, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 514)
  - Ogle, Jane, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 514)
  - O'Hearn, G. E., 1908, 1910 (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - Ohio State University, 1910 (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - Ohio Wesleyan University, 1903 (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - Okeson, Walter R., 1903, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - Olcott, P. P., 1917 (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - Oldham, John E.(*), 1910, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - O'Leary, C. J., 1902 (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - Oliver, E. W., 1916 (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - 100%, 1919 (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - Onman, A. Butler, undated (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - Ordway, Henry C., 1917 (Box 19, Folder 516)
  - Oregon Agricultural College, 1902, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 516)
  - Oregon, University of, 1917, 1919 (Box 19, Folder 516)
  - Oregonian, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 516)
  - Ornstein, Charles L., 1922 (Box 19, Folder 516)
  - Orton, George W.(*), 1900-1903, 1917, 1922 undated (Box 19, Folder 517)
  - Orton, R. E., 1894 (Box 19, Folder 517)
  - Osborn, Norris G., 1920 (Box 19, Folder 518)
  - O'Shea, M. V., 1916-1917 (Box 19, Folder 518)
  - Oskaloosa (Iowa) High School, 1894 (Box 19, Folder 518)
  - Oskamp, Nolting & Co., [189?] (Box 19, Folder 518)
  - Otis, Charles A., 1918 (Box 19, Folder 518)
  - Otis, E. A., 1892 (Box 19, Folder 518)
  - Outdoor Life, 1900 (Box 19, Folder 519)
  - Outing (*), 1891-1894, 1896, 1899-1903, 1905-1906, 1908-1911, 1915-1916, 1922, undated (Box 19, Folder 520-523)
  - Outlaw, C. W., 1919-1920 (Box 19, Folder 524)
  - Outlook, 1899, 1902, 1911-1912, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 524)
  - Overall, John H., 1915 (Box 19, Folder 525)
  - Overall, Sidney R., 1908 (Box 19, Folder 525)
  - Overton, W. S., 1917 (Box 19, Folder 525)
  - Oviatt, Edwin, 1902, undated (Box 19, Folder 525)
  - Owen, Ben, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 526)
  - Owsley, John E., 1905, 1908, 1910 (Box 19, Folder 526)
  - Pach Brothers, 1910 (Box 19, Folder 527)
  - Pacific College, 1894 (Box 19, Folder 527)
  - Pacific Union Club, 1892, 1894 (Box 19, Folder 527)
  - Packer Collegiate Institute, 1894 (Box 19, Folder 527)
  - Page, Arthur W.
    See: box 9, folder 251-253 See: box 27, folder 772
  - Page, Frank A., 1902 (Box 19, Folder 527)
  - Page, H. M., 1922, undated (Box 19, Folder 528)
  - Page (L. C.) & Company(*), 1898-1900, 1909,1912,1922 (Box 19, Folder 529-531)
  - Paget, E. M., 1924 (Box 19, Folder 532)
  - Paige, H. Ray, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 532)
  - Paine, Norman C., 1920 (Box 19, Folder 532)
  - Palmer, A. C., 1905 (Box 19, Folder 533)
  - Palmer, B. W., 1896 (Box 19, Folder 533)
  - Palmer, Lew R., 1920 (Box 19, Folder 533)
  - Palmer, Loren
  - Pan-American Exposition, 1901, 1900-1901 (Box 19, Folder 534)
  - Panama-Pacific International Exposition, 1914 (Box 19, Folder 534)
  - Pardee, J. S., 1908 (Box 19, Folder 535)
  - Pardee, William S., 1916 (Box 19, Folder 535)
  - Parish, Roswell, 1891 (Box 19, Folder 535)
  - Parker, Wilbur, 1889, 1894, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 535)
  - Parks, G. Elton, 1904 (Box 19, Folder 535)
  - Parks, George W., 1909 (Box 19, Folder 535)
  - Parr, Warren S., 1923 (Box 19, Folder 535)
  - Parrish, Harry B., 1899 (Box 19, Folder 535)
  - Parrish, Joseph L., 1916 (Box 19, Folder 535)
  - Patrick, G. T. W., 1902 (Box 19, Folder 536)
  - Patten, William E. and Mrs. William E.
  - Patterson, C. E.(*), 1898-1900, 1902, 1909 (Box 19, Folder 536)
  - Patterson, E. C.
  - Patterson, F. B., 1923 (Box 19, Folder 537)
  - Patterson, N. L., 1902 (Box 19, Folder 537)
  - Patterson, W. D., 1907 (Box 19, Folder 537)
  - Payne, Harry R., undated (Box 19, Folder 538)
  - Payson, Richard C., 1894 (Box 19, Folder 538)
  - Peabody, Endicott(*), 1894-1895, 1900-1917 (Box 19, Folder 539)
  - Peabody, R. A., 1887 (Box 19, Folder 539)
  - Peace, Edward G., 1889, 1894 (Box 20, Folder 540)
  - Pearse, C. G., 1898 (Box 20, Folder 540)
  - Peary, R. G., 1903 (Box 20, Folder 540)
  - Peck Bro's & Company, 1902, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 541)
  - Peck, Henry H., 1922 (Box 20, Folder 541)
  - Peck, John H., 1893-1894 (Box 20, Folder 541)
  - Peck, William E., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 541)
  - Peet, Walter B., 1899 (Box 20, Folder 542)
  - Peet, William, 1909-1910 (Box 20, Folder 542)
  - Pendleton, J. B., 1916 (Box 20, Folder 543)
  - Pendleton, Joseph B., 1911 (Box 20, Folder 543)
  - Penn Athletic Club, 1923-1924 (Box 20, Folder 543)
  - Pennsylvania State College, 1903, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 543)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, 1888, 1896, 1906, 1915, undated (Box 20, Folder 543)
  - People's Magazine, 1906 (Box 20, Folder 543)
  - Periodical Publishers' Association of America, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Perkins, Douglas, Jr., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Perkins, F. C., 1910 (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Perkins, T. C., 1891 (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Perrin, John B., 1909 (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Perrot, Frank R., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Perry, Gardner, 1894 (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Perry, Lawrence, 1916-1917 (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Perry, Philip, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Peters, Frank R., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 545)
  - Peters, N. M., 1901 (Box 20, Folder 545)
  - Peters, W. A., 1892 (Box 20, Folder 545)
  - Pettee, George D., 1894, 1909 (Box 20, Folder 545)
  - Phelps, Edward J., 1889, 1896, 1913, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 546)
  - Phelps, Mrs. William L., undated (Box 20, Folder 546)
  - Philbin, Stephen H., 1920 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Phillips Academy (Andover), 1895, 1900 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Phillips, Andrew W., 1894-1895, 1900, 1908 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Phillips, Charles W., 1908 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Phillips, Paul C., 1904-1906 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Phillips, Walter B., 1893-1894 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Phoenix Athletic Association, 1893 (Box 20, Folder 548)
  - Physical Culture, 1903, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 548)
  - Physical Training Teacher's Bureau, 1903 (Box 20, Folder 548)
  - Pierce, Palmer, E., 1903, 1905, 1909, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 549)
    See also: box 14, folder 388-389
  - Pierce, Thomas L., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 549)
  - Pigott, C. R., 1916 (Box 20, Folder 549)
  - Pike, David, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 550)
  - Pilcher, Campbell, 1901 (Box 20, Folder 550)
  - Pine Orchard Club, 1916 (Box 20, Folder 550)
  - Pipal, J. A., 1913, 1915-1920 (Box 20, Folder 550)
  - Pipen, L. A., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 550)
  - Pittsburg Dispatch, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 550)
  - Pittsburg Leader, 1906 (Box 20, Folder 550)
  - Pittsburgh Chronicle Telegraph, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 550)
  - Place, Victor M., 1903 (Box 20, Folder 551)
  - Platt & Peck Company(*), 1911-1912 (Box 20, Folder 551)
  - Playground & Recreation Association of America, 1920, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 552)
  - Poe, Edgar A., 1889 (Box 20, Folder 553)
  - Poe, John P., Jr., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 553)
  - Poe, S. Johnson, 1894-1895 (Box 20, Folder 553)
  - Polk, Frank L., 1917 (Box 20, Folder 554)
  - Pollard, J. E., 1924 (Box 20, Folder 554)
  - Pollard, J. W. H., 1908 (Box 20, Folder 554)
  - Porter, Josephine E. S., 1893, 1902-1903 (Box 20, Folder 555)
  - Porter, M. N., 1916 (Box 20, Folder 555)
  - Portland (Oregon) Amateur Athletic Club, 1894 (Box 20, Folder 555)
  - Post, Louis F., 1917-1918 (Box 20, Folder 556)
  - Potter & Putnam Co., 1898-1899, undated (Box 20, Folder 557)
  - Potter, Frank D., 1915 (Box 20, Folder 557)
  - Potter, J., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 557)
  - Potter, R. K., 1919 (Box 20, Folder 557)
  - Potter, Roderick, 1890 (Box 20, Folder 557)
  - Powel, Harford
  - Powell, A. L., 1916 (Box 20, Folder 558)
  - Powell, Albert H., 1911 (Box 20, Folder 558)
  - Powell, Walter, 1920-1922 (Box 20, Folder 558)
  - Poynter, Horace M., 1893 (Box 20, Folder 558)
  - Prather, T. J., 1894 (Box 20, Folder 559)
  - Pratt, Herbert L., 1919-1920 (Box 20, Folder 559)
  - Pratt, John T., 1895 (Box 20, Folder 559)
  - Press (*), 1892-1894, 1898-1903, 1907-1911, 1914, undated (Box 20, Folder 560-562)
  - Press Club (San Francisco), 1892 (Box 20, Folder 563)